Hey you know what we have some
Oye sabes qué que tenemos aquí una
news here that Jesús Manuel Ruiz broke
noticia que ha sacado Jesús Manuel Ruiz
today while people are giving likes
hoy mientras que la gente va dando like
and we reached 2500 likes for 3500
y llegamos a los 2500 likes para 3.500
likes from the newsstand okay It
likes de la kiosquera vale
turns out that Raquel Bollo has filed
Resulta ser que Raquel bollo ha puesto
a lawsuit that I think she
una demanda que esto creo que ella lo
dropped the other day no But she has filed
dejó caer el otro día no Pero ha puesto
a lawsuit to save me when she already said that
una demanda a sálvame cuando ya lo dijo
we are going to see the courts I am
que nos vamos a ver los juzgados estoy
a kiss a kiss Thank you very much thank you very much
un beso un beso Muchas gracias muchas
solaje thank you very much of course they
gracias solaje muchas gracias claro
are here for the exclusives that are
están aquí para las exclusivas que están
here like nowhere else no and it turns out
aquí como en ningún lado no y resulta
that I am seeing the name of the
ser que estoy viendo el nombre del
lawyer and it is the lawyer of a trial that I
abogado y es el abogado de un juicio Que
won recently Okay
gané hace poco Vale
my friend Zapatero My real friend eh go on those
mi amigo zapatero Mi amigo real eh anda
very good lawyers man Man the
eso muy buenos abogados hombre Hombre el
client that I had well was to lose
cliente que tenía pues era para perder
trial Yeah or yeah okay by the way of course
juicio Sí o sí vale que por cierto claro
eye that today I won a firm trial that I have
ojo que hoy gane un juicio en firme que
not remembered
no me he acordado
calm in a field Well I have several
tranquilo en un campo Pues tengo varios
pending I have several pending the
pendientes tengo varios pendientes del
result but today Hey they firm
resultado pero hoy Oigan ellos en firme
a trial that I already won in May and look at
un juicio que ya gané en mayo y fíjate
you how fast it has already come to me
tú que es rápido que ya me ha venido la
because the guy appealed it okay And
porque el tipo lo recurrió vale Y ya me
the final judgment has already come to me that he
ha venido la sentencia en firme que ya
can no longer appeal okay he is a friend
no puede recurrir vale que es un amigo
of Yo Juan who is Yo Juan The YouTuber
de yo Juan que anda yo Juan El youtuber
the YouTuber
el youtuber
threatened me that he was going to blow my
me amenazó con que me iba a reventar la
head off I already warned you then
cabeza ya te avisado luego
the guy threatened me to my face like a
el tío por toda la cara me amenazó como
guy I mean I know how to debate me whatever you
tío O sea yo que sé debateme lo que
want and the guy wanted to claim that since
quieras y el tío quería alegar que como
I am a gossip channel and controversial and a
yo soy un canal de chismes y polémico y
disaster
desastre
how much love eh I am that on YouTube
cuánto amor eh Yo es que en YouTube de
really I come here to look for
verdad Yo vengo aquí a buscar el amor
total love come on and these lawyers I
total vamos y estos abogados yo lo
know them because they are the lawyers of Jesús
conozco porque son los abogados de Jesús
de
de
Campanario Of course of course he has a lot of
campanario Claro claro lleva muchos
media issues Well I think that
temas mediáticos lleva Bueno yo creo que
in fact Manuel Ruiz, Jesús
de hecho el Manuel Ruiz el propio Jesús
Manuel himself who collaborates with us also
Manuel que colabora con nosotros también
with Antonio David, I think he started the
con Antonio David creo que él empezó la
practice of law in this one but I don't
práctica de abogados en este pero no me
pay much attention to it because I think that yes I have no
echo mucha cuenta porque creo que sí ni
idea I think he started the practice in this
idea creo que empezó la práctica en este
firm but I have won a lawsuit against
bufete pero yo le he ganado un juicio a
Mario because the client was not
Mario porque el cliente no tenía la
right simply and now we are
razón simplemente y ahora estamos
waiting for the sentence of the second
esperando la sentencia de la segunda
instance right to privacy,
instancia derecho a la intimidad al
honor and one's own image
honor y a la propia imagen
for  part of Raquel bollo
por parte de Raquel bollo
four months of television abuse
cuatro meses de maltrato televisivo
according to what Raquel bollo has been able to tell
según ha podido contar Raquel bollo a su
those closest to her the reason for this
gente más cercana la razón de este
constant pounding is her refusal
machaque constante es su negativa
or with me against me
o conmigo contra mí
with me against me totally what I would have
conmigo contra mí totalmente lo que me
liked not to specify a
hubiera gustado que no lo especifica un
little more
poco más
are the let's
son
say the reasons for the lawsuit
los digamos los motivos de la demanda
but
pero
more concrete or rather this program this
más concreto o sea este programa este
day this insult was said it was said
día se dijo este insulto se dijo se hizo
this accusation was made you know they don't go into
esta acusación sabe que no entran en
many details Because when you're
muchos detalles Porque cuando estás
suing it's
demandando
more
más conveniente guardártelo hasta el
convenient to keep it until trial or well there are people that there are people who in fact file lawsuits to publicize them you know and then they don't care about the result I've simply already filed it you know does something like that sound so strong that has been said about Raquel bollo man in the
haya dicho de Raquel bollo hombre en los
last few months yes there has been no not a
últimos meses sí que ha habido no no una
specific phrase but yes there has been a
frase concreta pero sí que ha habido un
time until she exploded In
un tiempo hasta que ella explotó En
those corridors that we saw here 200
aquellos pasillos que vimos aquí 200
times the video and we applauded it that
veces el vídeo y lo aplaudimos
was the product of
eso fue producto de
Sorry to interrupt you queen
Perdona que te interrumpa reina dos
twice sisuca I mean if suka has given 40
veces sisuca o sea si suka ha dado 40
members
miembros
we're going to get to two What kind of
vamos a llegar a los dos Qué tipo de
members does a  second wait
miembros espera un segundo espera
Marina one second a little dirty
Marina un segundo un poco sucia
members of the Channel girl Wait I'll
miembros del Canal chiquilla Espera yo
wait for you
te espero
What are you doing where are you going one second
Qué hace dónde va un segundo
a kiss bichiy I love you bike I
un beso bichiy se te quiere bici te he
saw you this afternoon there supporting me
visto esta tarde por ahí apoyándome
Thank you very much sweetheart beautiful mine I
Muchas gracias corazón guapísima mía se
love you How is my baby are you going to
te quiere Cómo está mi bebé le vas a
change his name now Avicii one second
cambiar el nombre ya Avicii un segundo
eh
eh
but it's that I'm trying because I
pero es que estoy intentando porque
want to read you something about WhatsApp but
quiero leeros una cosa del WhatsApp pero
as always I don't know what's going on I put it
es que como siempre no sé qué pasa que
But it doesn't link do I have to
lo pongo Pero no se vincula
buy you a laptop Marina
te tengo que comprar un portátil Marina
no no yes the laptop is divine but it
no no si el portátil está divino pero es
says extreme extreme encryption
que dice cifrado de extrema extremo
Wait it's for something I haven't told you
Espera es para una cosa no te la he
yet I'm telling you I'll tell you while you
todavía te lo digo te lo cuento mientras
're in black okay you won't
que estás en negro vale
believe it I swear I have
no te lo vas a creer no te lo juro que
n't looked it up I'm not
no lo he buscado que no me lo estoy
making it up a company contacted me
inventando me ha contactado una empresa
I'm not going to say the name yet when the day comes I'll put it But a company answered me wanting to give me a chair it's a lie I swear you won't see it come on I'm going to put it in the
la veréis vamos la voy a poner en la
corner but if I had that day one day
esquina pero si tuviera ese día un día
Well I was here doing the live
Pues estaba aquí haciendo el directo
with me sitting in the chair and what are you doing  to
conmigo en la silla sentada y qué vas a
do it's
hacer
not bad I have it there in the corner
no viene mal la tengo ahí en la esquina
because it's one day I'm with someone
porque es un día estoy con alguien que
Enrique is coming and I'm doing a live show with
viene Enrique que hago un directo con
Lorena so she can sit down mine
Lorena que se quede sentar la mía
many times I have to take out a
muchas veces tengo que sacar
certain chair more it's not there it is but damn
ciertaburete más no está ya está pero
[ __ ] it would have been nice if it had been
[__] [__] hubiera venido bien que
ago But well I prefer
hubiera sido hace Pero bueno yo prefiero
the chair that my lordship gave me who
la silla que me ha regalado a mi señoría
is much more of a man of course it's just that I do
que es mucho más hombre por supuesto es
n't know why wait it tells me
que no sé por qué espérate Me dice
extreme extreme encryption it doesn't let me how to
cifrado extremo extremo no me deja como
open it
abrirlo
so give it back this one no [ __ ] let's see this
pues devuelve esta no [__] a ver esta
chair is the most powerful the highest
silla es la más potente la de más
quality there is on the market right now I mean
calidad que hay en el mercado ahora
this chair is the ideal one you are
mismo o sea esta silla es la ideal estás
Yes already the prettiest and the highest quality there is right
Sí ya la más bonita y la de más calidad
now on the market for
que hay ahora mismo en el mercado para
my taste but the other chair is also
mi gusto pero la otra silla también es
very pretty you will see very handy and
muy bonita ya la veréis muy apañada y
also a company that sells things for
además una empresa que vende cosas para
offices and for studios very very
las oficinas y para los estudios muy muy
cool and people are going to like the
chulo y le va a gustar mucho la gente la
promo a lot when I do it they wanted to give me
promo cuando la haga me querían regalar
something else but something else doesn't fit but I'll
otra cosa pero otra cosa no me cabe pero
show it when I show it You'll
ya lo lo enseñaré cuando lo enseñe Vais
see it's very cool too it's very
a ver está muy chulo también está muy
pretty too it's very pretty What
bonito también está muy bonito Lo que
happens is that  yes it's true that the powerful
pasa que sí que es verdad que la potente
and the good one You know this but
y la buena Sabes Esta pero
damn another 500 and some euros I think it's not that I do
[__] otro 500 y pico de euro creo no es
n't know what's going on man what a
que no sé qué pasa tío vaya
promotion they didn't pay me they
promociónería no me la pagaron ellos me
paid me my honor
la pago mi señoría
Marina Hey
Marina Oye
but Marina
pero Marina
Javi I don't know what I'm doing What are you
Javi No sé qué estoy haciendo Qué hace
doing What are you doing See you later Marina we'll see you there Marina when you when you when you that leaves me here stranded okay Hi what is it that I want to read a conversation after with a person that I have spoken to on WhatsApp and it puts me on the
hablado en el WhatsApp y me pone en el
WhatsApp web that always works for me and it puts
WhatsApp web que siempre me va y me pone
WhatsApp encrypted end to end and it
WhatsApp cifrado de extremo a extremo y
doesn't let me open it on the computer in case I
no me deja abrirlo en el ordenador por
have tried to link but it doesn't even
si he intentado vincular pero es que no
give me the option I don't understand anything okay
me da ni la opción no entiendo nada vale
but what was it about Raquel bollo not
pero de qué era de lo de Raquel bollo no
about another one the other topic that we were going to the other
de otro del otro tema que íbamos al otro
topic that we were going to talk about but about
tema que íbamos a hablar pero de lo de
Raquel bollo let's
Raquel bollo yo vamos
see [Music] they said punishable things I think that
a ver dijeron cosas punibles yo creo que
maybe some guest more than some
a lo mejor algún invitado más que algún
collaborator is that of course you have to keep
colaborador es que claro tienes que
in mind that
tener en cuenta que
[Music]
[Música]
you have to keep in mind that she is
tienes que tener en cuenta que ella es
a person who  has lent to many
una persona que se ha prestado a muchos
when you are lending many to Leo it is
cuando tú estás prestado muchos a Leo es
more complicated that I am not saying that you have to
más complicado que no te digo que tengas
put up with everything but
que aguantar de todo pero
to his children to survivors but that
a sus hijos a supervivientes pero
does not give you the right at the moment that he
tampoco eso da derecho en el momento que
reappeared on the plate of
ya reapareció en el plato de
survivors to defend his children
supervivientes para defender a sus hijos
that evidently he charges normally The
que evidentemente cobra normalmente Los
Defenders No but in the case of Raquel I
Defensores No pero en el caso de Raquel
tell you from now on that yes I believe that the
te digo desde ya que sí yo creo que el
fact that she did not agree to
hecho de que ella no accediera a
participate in Sálvame we know with me
participar en sálvame sabemos el conmigo
against me Sálvame said Boom up to here I go I go
contra mí sálvame dijo Boom hasta aquí
the store ruined
voy yo voy yo la tienda arruinada lo de
the ruined the economic reasons the etc etc
la ruinada los motivos económicos el etc
etc in the end it
etc etc al final
undermines you looking looking looking looking
te va minando mirando mirando mirando
and it touches a little on what I do not know
mirando y roza un poco lo yo desconozco
if on a legal level if she has
si a nivel legal si ella lo ha
considered it And if this office that you know
considerado Y si este despacho que sabes
are good lawyers have pushed
que son buenos abogados han tirado para
forward something you will see I do not intuit they
adelante algo verán No intuyo a mí me
filed a lawsuit against me that did not go
pusieron una demanda que no tiraba para
forward or back from the moment
adelante ni para atrás desde el momento
of filing it but well, already,
de ponerla pero bueno ya ya
but let's see, for example, I remember that they
pero a ver yo por ejemplo me acuerdo que
said something but I think it was I do not know if it
dijeron algo pero creo que fue no sé si
was the father of the girl, the granddaughter or
fue el padre de la niña de la nieta no O
the grandson that they said  something like that he had
del nieto que dijeron algo así como que
taken the girl from him or that he had the
le había quitado la niña o que tenía la
girl, I don't remember, but he said something serious,
niña no me acuerdo pero dijo algo grave
but well, we'll see, we'll see.
pero bueno lo iremos viendo lo iremos
In the end, in a couple of years it
viendo al final esto en un par de años
turns out that, Hey, something was heard about that lawsuit
sale que Oye se supo algo de esa demanda
that Raquel supposedly won against
que supuestamente había ganado Raquel
Rocío Carrasco. I think
bollo en firme a Rocío Carrasco yo creo
nothing more was heard about that matter. I haven't heard anything about it, let's
que no se volvió a saber más de ese tema
see. I think not. And now, it was strange, it wasn't, he
a ver yo creo que no y ya pues raro no
told you, that's it. How strange that
era te dijo ya está no Qué raro que
Raquel hasn't come out to Designate,
Raquel no haya salido a Designar
then
entonces
no. Well,
no
nothing, well, we're still missing 500 likes. I
Pues nada pues nos faltan 500 like
'm going to post interviews.
todavía voy a poner entrevistas
Hey, how many do we have? 2,000, we're
Eh cuántos qué tenemos 2000 nos faltan
still missing 500.
500 todavía